A Guide to the Minutes of the Virginia Board of Nursing, 1975-2020.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Minutes of the Virginia Board of Nursing,
1975-2020.
The Library of Virginia
45475, 50099, 51027, 53644, 52676, 53932
Virginia. Dept. of Health Professions.
20.15 cu. ft.
Administrative Information
Arranged chronologically.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions
Acquisition Information
Accession 45475 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 4/7/2011.
Accession 50099 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 9/2/2011.
Accession 51027 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 9/18/2013.
Accession 52644 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 2/21/2019.
Accession 52676 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 4/1/2019.
Accession 53924 was transferred by the Dept. of Health Professions on 06/21/2023.
Historical Information
The Board of Examiners of Graduate Nurses was created by an act of Assembly May 1, 1903 to regulate the professional nursing of the sick in Virginia. The Board examined applicants, issued licenses and held the power to revoke licenses. At some point the name of the Board was changed to the Board of Examiners of Nurses. An act of Assembly dated March 17, 1970 created the Board of Nursing and repealed the chapter of the Code authorizing the Board of Examiners of Nurses. The new board has similar responsibilites, also including the accreditation of nursing curricula and promulgation of regulations.
The Dept. of Health Regulatory Boards was created by an act passed by the General Assembly on March 31, 1977, to provide administrative services to the health regulatory boards of the state. The boards continue to regulate their professions through the examination, licensing, and disciplining of the practitioners of health science. In 1986, the Dept. of Health Regulatory Boards became the Dept. of Health Professions. Its mission is to enhance the delivery of safe and competent health care by licensing qualified health care professionals, enforcing standards of practice, and providing information to both practitioners and consumers of health care services.
Scope and Content
Minutes, 2016-2020, include official minutes and related attachments documenting the meetings, activities, discussions, policy decisions and recommendations of the Virginia Board of Nursing. Includes minutes for the full board, standing committees and other groups, as well as records related to informal conference committees, special conference committees, telephone conferences, and formal hearings. This series also contains board meeting packets that may include agendas, bylaws, correspondence, draft minutes, legislation, presentations, regulations, reports, revenue and expenditure summaries, and town hall comments.
Includes minutes for the following: Agency Subordinate Informal Conferences, Bylaws Committee, Committee for the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, CORE Committee, Discipline Committee, Education Special Conference Committee, Massage Therapy Advisory Board, Nurse Aide Curriculum Committee, PICC Line Insertion and Removal Committee, Regulations Committee, as well as others.
Contents List
- Minutes of the Virginia Board of Nursing, 1975-2020.
  - Accession 45475 (1975-2005)., Extent: 4.55 cu. ft. (13 boxes)
    Includes original, signed minutes, 1990-2005. Full Board and hearings minutes were bound separately from Informal Conference Committee and Special Conference Committee minutes. Full Board minutes may include Education Special Conference Committee minutes and Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine minutes. Minutes, 1990-1992, Informal Conference Committee and Special Conference Committee only. Also includes Advisory and Special Committee minutes, 1975-2005 (Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, Education Special Conference Committee, and others). Minutes were transferred unbound and have been foldered.
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 Sept-Oct. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Full Board minutes, 1993 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 May-June. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 July-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 Sept-Oct. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 1994 Nov-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1994 Jan-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1994 May-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1994 Sept-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 Jan-Feb. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 Mar-Apr. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 May-June. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 July-Aug. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 Sept-Oct. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 1995 Nov-Dec. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1995 Jan-June. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1995 July-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 Jan-Feb. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 Mar-Apr. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 May-June. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 July-Aug. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 Sept-Oct. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Full Board minutes, 1996 Nov-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1996 Jan-Mar. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1996 Apr-June. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1996 July-Sept. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1996 Oct-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 Jan-Feb. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 Mar-Apr. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 May-June. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 July-Aug. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 Sept-Oct. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 1997 Nov-Dec. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 Jan-Feb. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 Mar-Apr. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 May-June. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 July-Aug. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 Sept-Oct. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1997 Nov-Dec. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 Jan-Feb. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 Mar-Apr. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 May-June. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 July-Aug. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 Sept-Oct. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 1998 Nov-Dec. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 Jan-Feb. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 Mar-Apr. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 May-June. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 July-Aug. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 Sept-Oct. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1998 Nov-Dec. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 Jan-Apr. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 May-Aug. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 Sept-Nov. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 Jan-Feb. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 May-June. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 1999 Nov-Dec. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 Jan-Mar. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 May-Aug. (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Full Board minutes, 1999 Sept-Dec. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 May-June. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 July-Aug. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 Sept-Oct. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2000 Nov-Dec. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Full Board minutes, 2001 Jan-Mar. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Full Board minutes, 2001 May-July. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Full Board minutes, 2001 Sept-Nov. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 Jan-Feb. (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 Mar-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 May-June. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 July-Aug. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 Sept-Oct. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2001 Nov-Dec. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 2002 Jan-Mar. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 2002 May-July. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 2002 Aug-Nov. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 Jan-Feb. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 Mar-Apr. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 May-June. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 July-Aug. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 Sept-Oct. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2002 Nov-Dec. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Full Board minutes, 2003 Jan-Mar. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Full Board minutes, 2003 May-Aug. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Full Board minutes, 2003 Sept-Dec. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 Jan-Feb. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 Mar-Apr. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 May-June. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 July-Aug. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 Sept-Oct. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2003 Nov-Dec. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Full Board minutes, 2004 Jan-Apr. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Full Board minutes, 2004 May-Aug. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Full Board minutes, 2004 Sept-Dec. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 Jan-Feb. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 Mar-Apr. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 May-June. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 July-Aug. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 Sept-Oct. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2004 Nov-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 2005 Jan-Mar. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 2005 May-Aug. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 2005 Sept-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 Jan-Feb. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 Mar-Apr. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 May-June. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 July-Aug. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 Sept-Oct. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Special Conference Committee minutes, 2005 Nov-Dec. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Ad Hoc Committee for the Review of the Nurse Practice Act, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Advisory Committee on Faculty Supervision During Home Health Visits, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Advisory Committee on Advance Placement, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Advisory Committee to Develop Guidelines for Training Public School Employees in the Administration of Insulin and Glucogon, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Boards of Nursing and Professional Counselors, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: By-laws Committee, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1978-1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1985-1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee on Continued Competence, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Committee to Review NCLEX-PN Test Items, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Disciplinary Issue Committee, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1993 May (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Education Special Conference Committee, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Executive Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Legislative Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Massage Therapy Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Nursing Education Advisory Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Nursing Education Advisory Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Nursing Practice Advisory Committee, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Nursing Practice Advisory Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Special Committee to Consider Regulations for Certified Nurse Aide Instructional Personnel, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Regulations Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Regulations Committee, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Advisory/Special Committees: Special Committee to Review Policies and Procedures Related to Impaired Nurses, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Accession 50099 (2006)., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box)
    Minutes, 2006, for the Full Board (also includes telephone conference calls and formal hearings), Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, Education Special Conference Committee, and Informal Conference/Special Conference Committees. Includes final, approved minutes, though not all include signatures.
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 May. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 2006 Nov-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine minutes, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Education Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 Sept-Oct. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Informal Conference and Special Conference Committee minutes, 2006 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accession 51027 (2008)., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box)
    Minutes, 2008, for the Full Board (also includes telephone conference calls and formal hearings), Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, Education Special Conference Committee, and Informal Conference Committees. Includes final, approved minutes with signatures.
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 Sept-Oct. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Full Board minutes, 2008 Nov-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine minutes, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Education Special Conference Committee minutes, 2008. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 Jan-Feb. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 Mar-Apr. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 May-June. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 Sept-Oct. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Informal Conference Committee minutes, 2008 Nov-Dec. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accession 52644 (2003-2005, 2008)., Extent: 3 cu. ft. (3 boxes)
    Minutes, 2003-2005, 2008, for the Full Board (which may also include Education Special Conference Committee, Nominations Committee, Nurse Practice Committee, formal hearing, informal conference, special conference, telephone conference minutes held during board week), Bylaws Committee, Committee of the Joint Board of Nursing and Medicine, Legislative Committee, Massage Therapy Advisory Board, Special Conference Committee for Regulation Review, and Task Force for Regulation of Medication Aides. Includes final, approved minutes without signatures, as well as draft, unapproved minutes. Full board minutes also include meeting packet attachments, including agendas, articles, revenue and expenditure summaries, correspondence, guidance documents, legislation, presentations, public hearing comments, regulations, and reports. Minutes, 2008, were foldered by month and include all types of board and committee minutes; original foldering and order has been maintained.
    - Special Conference Committee for Regulation Review, 2003 Jan 1. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2003 Jan 27-30. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2003 Jan 27-30. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Full Board, 2003 Mar 17-20. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Full Board (minutes only), 2003 May 12-14. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Full Board, 2003 July 14-16. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Full Board, 2003 Sept 22-24. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Full Board, 2003 Nov 17-20. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Full Board, 2004 Jan 27-29. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2004 Feb 18. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2004 Mar 22-25. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2004 Mar 22-25. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2004 Apr 21. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2004 May 17-20. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2004 May 17-20. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Full Board, 2004 July 19-21. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2004 Sept 20-23. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2004 Sept 20-23. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Full Board, 2004 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Massage Therapy Advisory Board, 2005 Jan 18. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2005 Jan 24-27. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2005 Jan 24-27. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Review Committee, 2005 Mar 4. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Full Board, 2005 Mar 14-17. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2005 Apr 13. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2005 May 16-19. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2005 May 16-19. (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Task Force for Regulation of Medication Aides, 2005 July 12. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2005 July 18-21. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2005 July 18-21. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Conference Call, 2005 July 26. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Task Force for Regulation of Medication Aides, 2005 Sept 7. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2005 Sept 19-22. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Full Board (folder 2 of 2), 2005 Sept 19-22. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine, 2005 Oct 19. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Task Force for Regulation of Medication Aides, 2005 Oct 25. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Full Board (folder 1 of 2), 2005 Nov 14-17. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Full Board (folder 2 fo 2), 2005 Nov 14-17. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - full Board, 2008 Jan 28-31. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Bylaws Committee, 2008 Feb 25. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 1 of 2), 2008 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 2 of 2), 2008 Mar. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 1 of 2), 2008 May. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 2 of 2), 2008 May. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Boards/Committees, 2008 June. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Boards/Committees (folder 1 of 2), 2008 July. (Box 3, Folder 9)